here we are at the international 2024
with Neil Fen had a real tough match uh
want to talk a little bit about it yeah
I guess uh to sum it up I wasn't
destined to win that one I mean uh nine
ball it's 10 to 15% luck and uh I freeze
him on five I jump the one in on 53 and
I freeze him on a ball next time I
shoots 5'5 cuz he kicks and flukes the
nine in then breaks the nine on the
break in two pokes so it's 55 then I I
go up six I break around 65 66 I win the
next game
76 or something Happ I can't remember
anyway I break I got scratched in the
corner got kicked in the corner and then
uh a couple of things where he misses a
jump and he leaves me an awkward combo I
I hung it up and then the last game he
uh he goes for another another jump and
he misses and he freezes me on the nine
so I'm like I I just couldn't do
anything I never had another shot from
76 not an open ball any not I couldn't
even play safe so nothing so well well
we want to say congratulations a great
finish uh was a pleasure to watch you
see back get excited and do some good
stuff the crowd is really cheering your
ey we want to say congratulations on
your finish thank appreciate it thank
you very much good job